upscalehype.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy | UpscaleHype

The following Privacy Policy covers all websites and any associated content including social network pages, email and RSS feeds owned, affiliated or operated by UpscaleHype, LLC. (“UpscaleHype”, “we”, “us”, “our”). We respect and understand your need for privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**By visiting UpscaleHype websites, submitting information or using any of our products and services, you are accepting the practiced outlined in this Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy covers UpscaleHype’s treatment of personal information that UpscaleHype gathers when you are on our websites and when you are using UpscaleHype services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers UpscaleHype’s treatment of any personal information that UpscaleHype’s business partners share with us. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to and from the website as well as the practices of third parties that UpscaleHype does not control or own, or individuals that UpscaleHype does not employ or manage.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time so check back often. Continued access of our websites by you will constitute your acceptance of the changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

**Information You Provide to Us**

The website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. This includes but is not limited to when you register to comment, receive newsletters, enter a sweepstakes and complete a survey. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features such as commenting or receiving newsletters. – Registration: In order to use select parts of our websites such as the comment section, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we may require your email address and date of birth. Optional information such as your referrer or time zone may also be requested.

**Automatic Information**

Our servers may automatically collect information about your computer when you visit our websites, including without limitation the website that referred you, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) and other usage and traffic information. UpscaleHype uses this statistical information to analyze trends, gather demographic information and administer our websites so we may provide improved web experiences to our readers. The information is not in a manner that would identify you personally. We may provide statistical information, not personal information, to our partners about how our users, collectively use our websites. We share this information to our partners, so that they may further understand the usage of their areas and our websites, so that they too could provide you with a better web experience. There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

**Cookies**

Cookies are messages given to a web browser by a web server that are placed in storage. Their purpose is to identify users and possibly prepare customized WebPages for them. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on our websites, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of our websites and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies. UpscaleHype does not collection personal information, and we do not combined information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is. Some of our advertisers may occasionally service you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don’t want any cookies, your web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refused cookies, some portions of the website may not function properly.  
**  
Sharing Information**

We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with your consent or to the entities described below: – Agents We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customers’ lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistant, and providing customer service. You hereby consent to our sharing of your personal information for the above purposes. – Business Transfers As our business changes and grow, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by UpscaleHype are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and about our website users may be among the transferred assets  
**  
Children and Parents**

Our websites are not meant for children, especially those under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

**Conditions of Use**

If you decide to visit UpscaleHype websites, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damagers, arbitration of disputes and application of United States law.

**Third Party Websites**

UpscaleHype may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to UpscaleHype websites. These other websites are not under UpscaleHype control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from UpscaleHype websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and UpscaleHype is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at UpscaleHype websites, please send a detailed message to contact@upscalehype.com. Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
